<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<BattleItems>
    <Item>
        <ID>0</ID>
        <Name>X Attack</Name>
        <Type>0</Type>
        <Effect>Raises the Attack of a Pokémon currently in battle by 1 level.</Effect>
        <Description>An item that sharply boosts the Attack stat of a Pokémon during a battle. It wears off once the Pokémon is withdrawn.</Description>
    </Item>
    <Item>
        <ID>1</ID>
        <Name>X Defense</Name>
        <Type>1</Type>
        <Effect>Raises the Defense of a Pokémon currently in battle by 1 level.</Effect>
        <Description>An item that sharply boosts the Defense stat of a Pokémon during a battle. It wears off once the Pokémon is withdrawn.</Description>
    </Item>
    <Item>
        <ID>2</ID>
        <Name>X Sp. Atk</Name>
        <Type>2</Type>
        <Effect>Raises the Special Attack of a Pokémon currently in battle by 1 level.</Effect>
        <Description>An item that sharply boosts the Sp. Atk stat of a Pokémon during a battle. It wears off once the Pokémon is withdrawn.</Description>
    </Item>
    <Item>
        <ID>3</ID>
        <Name>X Sp. Def</Name>
        <Type>3</Type>
        <Effect>Raises the Special Defense of a Pokémon currently in battle by 1 level.</Effect>
        <Description>An item that sharply boosts the Sp. Def stat of a Pokémon during a battle. It wears off once the Pokémon is withdrawn.</Description>
    </Item>
    <Item>
        <ID>4</ID>
        <Name>X Speed</Name>
        <Type>4</Type>
        <Effect>Raises the Speed of a Pokémon currently in battle by 1 level.</Effect>
        <Description>An item that sharply boosts the Speed stat of a Pokémon during a battle. It wears off once the Pokémon is withdrawn.</Description>
    </Item>
    <Item>
        <ID>5</ID>
        <Name>X Accuracy</Name>
        <Type>5</Type>
        <Effect>Raises the accuracy of a Pokémon currently in battle by 1 level.</Effect>
        <Description>An item that sharply boosts the accuracy stat of a Pokémon during a battle. It wears off once the Pokémon is withdrawn.</Description>
    </Item>
    <Item>
        <ID>6</ID>
        <Name>Dire Hit</Name>
        <Type>6</Type>
        <Effect>Raises the critical hit ratio of a Pokémon currently in battle by 1 level. Does not stack with itself or Focus Energy.</Effect>
        <Description>An item that raises the critical-hit ratio greatly. It can be used only once and wears off if the Pokémon is withdrawn.</Description>
    </Item>
    <Item>
        <ID>7</ID>
        <Name>Guard Spec.</Name>
        <Type>7</Type>
        <Effect>Prevents stat reduction by opponents' moves for the user's party for five turns.</Effect>
        <Description>An item that prevents stat reduction among the Trainer's party Pokémon for five turns after it is used in battle.</Description>
    </Item>
</BattleItems>